Support for NPR Music comes from Capital
1, proud supporters of NPR Music and the
Tiny Desk Contest. What's in your
wallet? Learn more at capital1.com.
Heat.
All
right.
Engine.
us.
Judah
for our
fire.
We
launch
somewhere. Where
the wrong
so many times. Let's
grab
your
fire.
Beware of fighting
Get
surrender.
Spare this one.
Spare this one. SP this bad.
>> Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Very kind.
We are Nate Palm Deaf for the
uninitiated
just in case you might be wondering. So,
welcome one and all. Nice to see you.
Let me say we are here to heartily
support public access broadcasting.
>> Unfortunately,
it is under attack from all sides in the
UK as well as over here. And we have to
take care of it. It's precious. It has
to has to be preserved. So, um, next up,
we're going to do something along the
same lines about everyday fear and
paranoia. Some of it justifiable, some
of it you can let it slip to one side.
This one's called Everyday Pox. Thank
you.
SW
forune you
here
every night
They know you
want
you
die.
I protect you.
They die.
It's a group of
the
everyday boss.
Every day, boss.
Every day. Every day. Box.
Every [__] fight.
A
every time
[__]
bursting longs to the last gasp. Last
gasp. Last gasp. Bursting long to the
last gasp. Last gas. Last gas. Bursting
logs to the last gas. Last gas. Last
gas. Last.
Cross
I'm
join
me
Get me out.
talking
me
in.
defeated
me.
Oh my god.
What the
Thank you very much. So, next up, we're
going to do something really [__]
rare. Something resembling musical
nicities, which which in the context of
napal death sounds utterly ludicrous,
and it is, of course. But this next
little diddy perhaps approaches the
meest hint of musical beauty.
The meest hint. This one's called Aarl.
Thank you.
When the dark go
to be the master are all reveal
of guil
from the dark we all take the I can do
what we We
take a
day
to avo.
In the end of the world
champion
in the west
we gave away a break
but It's just the mind of one
of the
danger. Your boys
in the
world
Yeah.
Dad.
Thank you. Stick that last one in your
pipe and [__] smoke it.
Right, it appears
we have a couple of songs left. Short
but sweet. That is the name of the game.
So, we're going to take you back to um
8687,
very first Nate Palm Death album. Okay.
Um so, thanks to everybody for
assembling today. I see a couple of old
friends, Richard over there trying to
stay incognito. But, uh thank you all
for coming. Hope you've enjoyed it.
Something different for us, but very
neat. Very neat. Um this one's a title
track of that first album. This one's
called Scum. Thank you,
Why
Run.
[__]
A
let's everybody. Oh, he's got
heat.
Ly.
Good night. Thank you.
Thanks for watching. Support for NPR
music comes from Riven, makers of all
electric adventure vehicles, including
the R1S three row SUV. More at riv.com.
A quick update before you go, we're
doing another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter
by September 12th, 2026, and you and a
friend could win a free trip to DC to
see a Tiny Desk concert live in person.
You even get to choose which upcoming
show you want to see, and it's
completely free to enter. Just go to
npr.org/tiny. org/tinyes giveaway.
Entering is completely free, but you can
get more entries by snagging some
limited edition Tiny merch or by making
a special donation to the NPR network.
Learn more and enter today at
npr.org/tinyes
giveaway.